scratchmania.com 2017-11-03

# ScratchMania - Privacy and Security Policy

We at ScratchMania.com hold your privacy and security in the highest regard. We are committed to the utmost level of respect to ensure and protect your privacy.

**Account Information:**

Your information is important to us. All the Account Information that you supply during the account creation process is kept strictly confidential. When your information passes from your computer to our server, we ensure that sensitive data is transferred securely over the internet.

ScratchMania.com utilizes the latest 128-bit Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology. The data is transferred to our secure server, which is protected by the most recently updated firewall.  
Your privacy is important to us. We do NOT share your information. Not with any third party, or company or organization. This information includes your e-mail addresses and other personal details supplied upon registration.

ScratchMania.com is committed to "CARE" - Customers Are Really Everything. We use the collected personal details and information only for its intended purpose, such as; allowing us to communicate and send you your cash-outs. We also might contact you through E-mail addresses to provide members with information regarding new software updates, promotional material.

Your Personal Information collected by us is kept strictly confidential we collect your personal information when you register to become a member of our site; voluntarily provide it when you use the site; we may use it when you communicate with us.

If you register to become a customer of our services, we may use the personal information that you provide for billing purposes, and to administer and manage your account and provide promotional updates regarding such products or services as contemplated above. We may occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, including without limitation, identity verification, payment processing and the provision of software. We will only provide these companies that information which is reasonably required to perform the service, and they will be prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.

Generally, when any of our third-party contractors or partners collect and/or have access to your personal information we require that they adhere to our stated privacy policies and protect the confidentiality of your personal information. We collect e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail.

To unsubscribe from our mailing list, please send our support team (support (at) ScratchMania.com) a blank e-mail with the text "remove" in the subject. Help and support is also available. We have implemented a professional customer support team ready to assist you 24 hours a day, 7 days a week. Please do not hesitate to contact the ScratchMania.com team. Just click on contact us.

**How Do I Agree to the Privacy Policy?**

This Privacy Policy is an integral part of Hermione Limited and ScratchMania.com User Agreement. Accordingly, when you check the "I Accept" button or access or use the ScratchMania.com website, you automatically agree to our collection, use, and disclosure of your confidential information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree or are not comfortable with any part of this Privacy Policy, you may not use the ScratchMania.com website.

**Winnings:**

We believe that your good fortune is your business. We keep all our members' winnings and cash-outs strictly confidential and private. Our winnings information is stored in a secure operating environment.

**Payment Processing:**

Our payment process is focused on user friendly procedure and comfortable use through a variety of payment methods. ScratchMania.com offers a wide host of deposit options and fast cash outs. All the options are user friendly and highly secure. All credit and debit card transactions are processed by Hermione Limited which is a corporation incorporated under the laws of Cyprus. Naturally you may have additional questions. That’s great. please do not hesitate to contact our Customer Support center at any time, our Customer Service representatives will be more than happy to assist you.

**Advertisements:**

The Company may, from time to time, offer you special promotions. These promotions may be notified to you by various means, including but not limited to (i) email, (ii) telephone, (iii) SMS (iv) additional windows opening from within the game platform. Promotions begin at 00:00 and end at 23:59 UTC on specified dates, unless stated otherwise in the promotions.

**Terms & Conditions:**

As part of the account registration process, We also offer our customers registering with us the opportunity to "opt out" from keeping them informed of future events, offers and promotions from ScratchMania. Visitors interested in opting out can simple click on the unsubscribe button in our marketing mailers or should 'uncheck' the relevant box in the registration process. You may update Your marketing preferences at any time through by contacting our friendly Customer agents.

If you have chosen to receive information on future events, offers and promotions by SMS message to your cellular telephone, You may "opt out" from receiving such information at any time by sending an email to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#3c4f494c4c534e487c6f5f4e5d485f54715d52555d125f5351) or contacting our customer service agents replying with the word "STOP". To opt out of third party analytics please email us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#3744424747584543776454455643545f7a56595e561954585a) and include your device identifier, and once processed, our third party analytics provider will discontinue any analytics  on that particular device.

About us

Hermione Ltd.

Inomenon Ethnon 44, Larnaka 6042, Cyprus

This Privacy and Security Terms & Conditions has been drafted in English. In the event of any discrepancy between the meanings of any translated versions of this Policy and the English language version, the meaning of the English language version shall prevail.

 Version 1

Dated 01/11/2015
